Mahmoud Abdulrhman

Grand Terrace, CA 92313

Email: Mahmoudtheeb@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mahmoud-abdulrhman-93964328

Github: https://github.com/MahmoudAbdulrhman

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full-Stack Web Developer specializing in the MERN stack. Lifelong dedication to learning, highly skilled interpersonal communicator, and servant leader with the technical skills to deliver projects on time and under budget. Known amongst peers as calm under pressure, communicative, easy to work with and happy to help.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

UI Web Technologies: React.js, Express, Node, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, JSX, AJAX, jQuery, Bootstrap, OAuth, Google Authentication

Databases: MySql + Sequelize, MongoDB + Mongoose, Firebase, GraphQl,Apollo

Version Controls: Git, Github, Gitlab

APPLICATIONS

Study Mouse | https://thawing-castle-75058.herokuapp.com/

- **Summary**: Study Mouse is a collaborative online resource where users can trade highly specific information through asking questions and getting answers for them. The likes of stack overflow and quora.
- Focus: DataBase, controle, debugging, and testing.
- Tech: Bulma, JavaScript,HTML,Restful APi,NodeJs, MySql, Express Js, Handlebars.

Shop-Shop | https://murmuring-brook-60929.herokuapp.com/ |

https://github.com/MahmoudAbdulrhman/shop-shop,

- **Summary**: This is a full MERN project consisting of a full functioning website that allows users to sign up, log in, buy/add to cart/ remove from cart in a wide-range collection of products, Also we used stripe to submit payment.
- Focus: Full design, development.
- Tech: MongoDB, Node.js, MERN, Bootstrap, JavaScript, NodJs, Redux, stripe

TransferCard | https://transfercard.herokuapp.com/ |

https://github.com/itsrheine/transferCard,

- Summary: Travel with ease with our new contactless virtual train ticket, transferCard.
- Focus: Authentication, DataBase, globale state
- Tech: MongoDB and Mongoose, graphql, Testing, Stripe, PWA and Redux, Heroku Deployment, MERN.

Budget Tracker | https://hidden-anchorage-26025.herokuapp.com/ | https://github.com/MahmoudAbdulrhman/-Budget- Tracker- -PWA-/blob/main/package.json ,

- **Summary**:Budget Tracker is a progressive web application that allows users to track their budgets by adding expenses and deposits to their budget through the "Add/Subtract Funds" buttons.
- Focus:Full Design.
- Tech: MongoDB and Mongoose, Pwa.

Education

- UC Berkeley Extension January 2021 Full stack web developer
- Al-Zaytoonah University of Jordan June 2010 Bachelors of Arts in Graphic Design

Work Experience

Sales Associate

Ermenegildo Zegna - Cabazon, CA March 2019 to Present

- Consistently and effectively networks to attract new customers and develop a customer database
- Consults with customers to discover their needs by exploring customer preferences and occasions for which the customers are shopping.
- Create opportunities for customers to experience multiple Zegna brands, products and "total looks" through demonstrating relevant yet personalized mix and match options.
- Utilize company provided (iPod/iPad) technology to offer a complete and integrated luxury experience. Collects useful and accurate customer data and information in accordance with Zegna CRM procedures and guidelines.
- Cultivates future customer connections with Zegna (e.g. CRM after-sales activities including Thank You notes and Follow-up phone calls).
- Utilize CRM software as the primary tool for after-sales communication Drive and perform onsite audits of store physical inventories
- Actively communicate customer, product, and other store information within the store team to ensure customer and business needs are met.

• When required support the orientation of new staff through acting as a learning coach or "buddy" if assigned by the Store Manager.

Sales Associate

Citizen Watch Store - Cabazon, CA August 2018 to Present

• Help open the store and maintain organization and cleanliness • Customer service -bilingual in English and Arabic • Take part in store inventory to keep track of merchandise

Assistant Manager

Fragrance Outlet - Cabazon, CA November 2016 to January 2019

- Develop customer relationships to drive additional business and maintain customer satisfaction Showcase perfumes to customers and tell them about latest promotions and discounts
- Explain to customers about the product they are buying and the properties of the perfume
- Gather information about customer satisfaction about product
- Involved in product marketing to customers

EDUCATION

- UC Berkeley Extension January 2021 Full stack web developer
- Al-Zaytoonah University of Jordan June 2010 Bachelors of Arts in Graphic Design